Ankit Chopade

https://aboutout.github.io/

PROFILE

E-mail: chopadeankit1997@gmail.com Mobile: (+91) 8149828009

Shri Guru Gobind Singhji Institute of Engineering and Technology graduate with Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering. Held internship focusing on Data Science and Machine Learning. Served on several college and fraternal committees. Built additional Data Science capabilities via online courses, off-campus courses and volunteering efforts.

EDUCATION

Shri Guru Gobind Singhji Institute of Engineering and Technology

Nanded,IND Aug. 2015 -- May. 2019

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering; CGPA: 8.17

PUBLICATIONS

- Seven Class Classification of Skin Lesions by using Incremental Convolutional Neural Network in Python ICAEEC-2019
- Classification of Skin Lesions by using Extended Incremental Convolutional Neural Network

ICCCT-2019

SKILLS & RELEVANT COURSEWORK

- Languages: Python(dash, plotly, matplotlib, keras, sklearn), Java, SQL, PHP, C, JavaScript
- Techniques: Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Data Science, Computer Vision, Data Structure & Algorithms
- Tools/Packages: OpenCV, Spring, Hibernate, Maven, Latex, RPA- Ui Path, Oracle, Tableau
- Courses: Probability and Statistics in Data Science using Python, Python for Data Science, Python of Research, Cyber Security, Distributed Computing, Artificial Neural Network

EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist Intern

Mar. 2019 -- May. 2019

- > Work on ETL process, Business Intelligence Tools-Tableau and formulated Key Performance Indicators based on data
- > Developed dashboards for many domains like Social Media and developed modules for Business Intelligence ToolAI-Mind
- **Assistant System Engineer-Trainee**

June. 2019 -- Present

 \triangleright \triangleright

PROJECTS

• Chennai Water Management

Technology: Python(matplotlib, pandas, numpy)

> Visualize the water need / usage of the city, Identify whether the water sources availability will be able to meet the needs till the subsequent monsoon, How bad is the current water crisis compared to previous years.

Analyzing Space Launches with Python

Nov. 2018 -- Feb. 2019

- Technology: Python(seaborn, matplotlib, pandas, numpy)
- > In this project the launches done by various countries are analyze on various distinct parameters like launch dates, mission, type, agency, etc and four conclusions are drawn.
- The launch agencies are also analyzed on parameters like count of launches, type, class, etc.

Paperless Submission

Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Java, JSP

Aug. 2017 - Nov. 2017

- > This is a Web Application where Students can compile and run different types of programming languages (C, C++, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL) source code and can store their daily assignments provided during the practical sessions online.
- > Faculties can access the status of assignments of students by providing online grades automatically based on the Test Cases.

Medica Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Java, JSP

May. 2017 -- June 2017

- > I have developed the Web Application (Medica) where the patient can have the record of all its Medical Reports generated by any Medical authorities. The patient account is validated by its UID Number. The Medical authorities can access the patient account by using patient UID Number and UID of medical authorities.
- > Patient can access his account by using his/her UID Number and Password.

VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES & OTHER COOL THINGS TO KNOW ABOUT ME

Official Head Utsav 2018

Responsible for total arrangement college cultural event. Lead more than 500 students.

Student's Co-ordinator Pragyaa 2017

Responsible for managing on ground activities and arrangements. Lead more than 100 students.